<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Hiraya.org</title>
    <link href="https://Hiraya.org/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://Hiraya.org" />
    <updated>2020-11-19T21:02:42+08:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>SweetSeclusion</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://Hiraya.org</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Welcome to Hiraya International</title>
        <author>
            <name>SweetSeclusion</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://Hiraya.org/welcome-to-hiraya-international/"/>
        <id>https://Hiraya.org/welcome-to-hiraya-international/</id>

        <updated>2020-11-19T21:02:42+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     "Hiraya" is an ancient Tagalog word that means "dreams and hopes" and here at Hiraya International, we dream of bridging the cultures&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <figure class="post__image"><em style="font-size: 14px; color: var(--text-editor-body-color); font-family: var(--font-base); font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/1/collaboration-community-cooperation-461049-1024x829-md-3.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 48em) 100vw, 768px" srcset="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/1/responsive/collaboration-community-cooperation-461049-1024x829-md-3-xs.jpg 300w ,https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/1/responsive/collaboration-community-cooperation-461049-1024x829-md-3-sm.jpg 480w ,https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/1/responsive/collaboration-community-cooperation-461049-1024x829-md-3-md.jpg 768w"  alt="" width="768" height="622"></figure><br>"Hiraya"</em><span style="font-size: 14px; color: var(--text-editor-body-color); font-family: var(--font-base); font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);"> is an ancient Tagalog word that means </span><em style="font-size: 14px; color: var(--text-editor-body-color); font-family: var(--font-base); font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);">"dreams and hopes"</em><span style="font-size: 14px; color: var(--text-editor-body-color); font-family: var(--font-base); font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);"> and here at Hiraya International, we dream of bridging the cultures of France, Romania, and the Philippines through different programs that highlight the three countries uniqueness.</span></p>
<div class="wp-block-columns has-2-columns is-main-message">
<div class="wp-block-column">
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph {"customFontSize":14} --></p>
<p class="has-custom-size" style="font-size: 14px;">Some of the things we want to promote are the Filipino Martial Arts, Romanian Folk Dances, and French organic agriculture.</p>
</div>
<div class="wp-block-column">
<p><!-- /wp:image --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
</div>
<p><!-- /wp:column --></p>
</div>
<p><!-- /wp:columns --></p>
<p><!-- wp:coblocks/row {"columns":2,"layout":"66-33","coblocks":{"id":"77123959945"}} --></p>
<div class="wp-block-coblocks-row coblocks-row-77123959945" data-columns="2" data-layout="66-33">
<div class="wp-block-coblocks-row__inner has-medium-gutter has-no-padding has-no-margin is-stacked-on-mobile"><!-- wp:coblocks/column {"width":"64.63","coblocks":{"id":"771240515"}} -->
<div class="wp-block-coblocks-column coblocks-column-771240515" style="width: 64.63%;">
<div class="wp-block-coblocks-column__inner has-no-padding has-no-margin"><!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
</div>
</div>
<p><!-- /wp:coblocks/column --></p>
<p><!-- wp:coblocks/column {"width":"34.37","coblocks":{"id":"771240519"}} --></p>
<div class="wp-block-coblocks-column coblocks-column-771240519" style="width: 34.37%;">
<div class="wp-block-coblocks-column__inner has-no-padding has-no-margin"><!-- wp:search {"label":""} /-->
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
</div>
</div>
<p><!-- /wp:coblocks/column --></p>
</div>
</div>
<p><!-- /wp:coblocks/row --></p>
<p><!-- wp:separator --></p>
<hr class="wp-block-separator">
<p><!-- /wp:separator --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph {"customFontSize":14} --></p>
<div class="gallery-wrapper"><div class="gallery"  data-is-empty="false" data-columns="3">
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/1/gallery/3.jpeg" data-size="768x1024"><img loading="lazy" src="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/1/gallery/3-thumbnail.jpeg" alt="" width="720" height="960"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/1/gallery/2.jpeg" data-size="768x1024"><img loading="lazy" src="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/1/gallery/2-thumbnail.jpeg" alt="" width="720" height="960"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/1/gallery/4.jpeg" data-size="768x1024"><img loading="lazy" src="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/1/gallery/4-thumbnail.jpeg" alt="" width="720" height="960"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/1/gallery/1.jpeg" data-size="1024x768"><img loading="lazy" src="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/1/gallery/1-thumbnail.jpeg" alt="" width="720" height="540"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/1/gallery/6.jpeg" data-size="1024x548"><img loading="lazy" src="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/1/gallery/6-thumbnail.jpeg" alt="" width="720" height="385"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/1/gallery/7.jpeg" data-size="1024x768"><img loading="lazy" src="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/1/gallery/7-thumbnail.jpeg" alt="" width="720" height="540"></a></figure>
</div></div>
<p style="font-size: 14px;"><strong><br>HIRAYA INTERNATIONAL</strong> is an association, bridging Romania, France, and the Philippines through<br>knowledge sharing, culture and arts participation, and sustainable development and also to cultivate friendship and collaboration between Filipinos, French, and Romanians through cultural, artistic, gastronomic, and sporting events and projects that highlight the uniqueness of each culture.<br><br>To promote involvement in activities that supports sustainable development. to exchange knowledge in history, culture, arts, science, sports, and tourism; to build connections with cultural, professional, scientific, artistic, humanitarian, and literary groups; to create partnerships with financial-economic fields or cultural sponsorship; to create cultural exchange and dialogue through conferences, meetings, and talks.<br><br>To bolster artistic exchange through art events, sporting events, concerts, and exhibitions; to implement various programs in the arts like music, (sport, traditional and modern) dance and martial arts fit for different age groups; to participate in competitions, festivals, or congresses organized to promote artistic and cultural programs. To promote Filipino Martial Arts in Europe, Philippines and around the world.<br><br>To create public awareness of socio-political, community and environmental issues; to Promote a responsible attitude towards the environment among the general public; to promote, in cooperation with other specialized agencies, sustainable designs in the community; to promote nonpolluting technologies, renewable energy sources and organic farming; to support scientific researches that creates positive social and environmental impact; to support sustainable products and sustainable agricultural practices.<br><br>To organize humanitarian aid in the event of natural disasters, wars, and famines; to implement projects such as the construction of spaces that serve orphanages, nursing homes, social centers, homeless shelters, and or rehabilitation centers; to support projects of accessibility, sport and cultural activities for handicapped and marginalized sector.<br>To promote the culinary arts of each country through exhibitions and fairs; and to facilitate gastronomic<br>experiences with each culture; To promote the traditional food products of each country.<br><br></p>
<p><!-- /wp:coblocks/gallery-carousel --></p>
<p><!-- wp:separator --></p>
<hr class="wp-block-separator">
<p><!-- /wp:separator --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph {"customFontSize":14} --></p>
<p class="has-custom-size" style="font-size: 14px;"><br><br><strong>L’Association HIRAYA INTERNATIONAL</strong> c’est une association qui se propose de réunir la Roumanie, la<br>France et Philippines par l’échange des connaissances, les participations dans l’Arts et la culture et le<br>développement durable ainsi que cultiver l’amitié et la collaboration entre les citoyens philippinais, français, et roumains, à travers des évènements et projets culturelles, artistiques, gastronomiques et sportifs, pour mettre en évidence chaque culture.<br><br>Promouvoir l’implication dans les activités qui soutienent le développement durable; encourager l’échange de connaissances en histoire, culture, arts, science, sports et tourisme; établir des liens avec les groupes culturelles, professionnels, scientifiques, artistiques, humanitaires et littéraires; créer des parteneriats à domaines financier- économique ou des sponsorisations sportives; faciliter et de créer l’échange et le dialogue cuturel dans le cadre des conférences, rencontres ou débats.</p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph {"customFontSize":14} --></p>
<p class="has-custom-size" style="font-size: 14px;">Soutenir les échanges à travers des évenements artistiques, sportifs, concerts et expositions; implémenter divers programmes dans le domaine artistique comme la musique, la danse (traditionnel, modern, sportif) et les arts martiaux par diverses tranches d’âge; participer à des compétitions, festivals, ou d’organiser des congrés pour promouvoir des programmes artistiques et culturelles.<br><br>Promouvoir les Art Martiaux Philippins en Europe, Philippines et au monde entier.<br>Créer une prise de conscience publique concernant les problèmes socio-politiques, communautaires et de<br>l’environnement et de promouvoir une attitude responsible vis-à-vis de la nature dans le cadre de la population et de promouvoir, en coopération avec d’autres Agences et Organismes spécialisés, un design durable dans les communautées; Soutenir les recherches scientifiques qui ont un impact positif social et environemental, de promouvoir les technologies non-polluantes, les énergies renouvables et l’agriculture organique, les produits et les pratiques agricoles soutenables.<br><br>Organiser des campagnes d’aide humanitaire dans l’éventualité des désastres naturels, guerres, ou famine et d’implémenter des projets comme la contruction des espaces comme des orphelinates, asiles, centres sociaux, des abris pour les sdf, et des centres de réabilitation. De soutenir des projets d’accesssibilité, activités sportives et culturelles pour personnes handicapées et le secteur de la population marginalisé.<br><br>Promouvoir les arts culinaires de chaque pays à travers des expositions et des foires; faciliter les expériences gastronomiques avec chaque culture; Promouvoir les produits alimentaires traditionnels de chaque pays.<br><br></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph {"customFontSize":14} --></p>
<p class="has-custom-size" style="font-size: 14px;">Asociaţia <strong>HIRAYA INTERNATIONAL</strong> îşi propune să unească România, Franţa şi Filipine prin intermediul<br>schimbului de cunoştiinţe, participarea în arte şi cultură, şi dezvoltarea durabilă si de asemenea de a cultiva<br>prietenia şi colaborarea între cetăţenii filipinezi, francezi şi cei români prin evenimente şi proiecte culturale,<br>artistice, gastronomice şi sportive, care să scoată în evidenţă unicitatea fiecărei culturi.<br>Să promoveze implicarea în activităţi care să sprijine dezvoltarea durabilă a relatiilor intre cele trei state; să<br>incurajeze schimbul de cunoştiinţe în istorie, cultură, arte, ştiinţă, sport, şi turism; să construiască legături cu grupuri culturale, profesionale, ştiinţifice, artistice, humanitare şi literare; să creeze parteneriate cu domenii financiar-economice sau sponsorizări sportive; să faciliteze si creeze schimbul şi dialogul cultural în cadrul unor conferinţe, întâlniri şi discuţii.<br><br>Să susţină schimburi artistice prin intermediul evenimentelor artistice, sportive, concerte şi expoziţii; să<br>implementeze diferite programe în domenii artistice cum ar fi muzica, dansul (tradiţional, sportiv sau modern) şi artele marţiale pentru diferite segmente de vârstă; să participe în competiţii, festivaluri, sau congrese organizate pentru a promova programe artistice şi culturale. Să promoveze artele marţiale filipineze în Europa, Filipine şi restul lumii.<br><br>Să creeze o conştientizare publică asupra nivel problemelor socio-politice, comunitare şi de mediu şi să promoveze o atitudine responsabilă faţă de mediul înconjurător în cadrul populaţiei şi să promoveze, în cooperare cu alte agenţii şi organisme specializate, un design durabil în cadrul comunităţii; Să sprijine cercetările ştiinţifice care au un impact pozitiv social şi de mediu, să promoveze tehnologiile non-poluante, sursele de energie renovabile şi agricultura organică; să sprijine produse şi practici agricole sustenabile.<br><br>Să organizeze campanii de ajutorare umanitara în eventualitatea unor dezastre naturale, războaie, sau foamete şi să implementeze proiecte cum ar fi construcţia de spaţii care să servească drept orfelinate, azile, centre sociale, adăposturi pentru cei fără adăpost, sau centre de reabilitare. Să sprijine proiecte de accesibilitate, activităţi sportive şi culturale pentru persoanele cu handicap şi sectorul de populaţie marginalizată.<br><br>Să promoveze artele culinare ale fiecărei ţări prin intermediul de târguri şi expoziţii; şi să faciliteze experienţe gastronomice cu fiecare cultură; Să promoveze produsele şi mâncarea tradiţionale caracteristice<br>fiecărei ţări;</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Hiraya FMA</title>
        <author>
            <name>SweetSeclusion</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://Hiraya.org/hiraya-fma/"/>
        <id>https://Hiraya.org/hiraya-fma/</id>

        <updated>2020-11-02T14:42:47+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     A project aiming at promoting Filipino Martial Arts, documenting my journey / training sessions. 
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <ul>
<li class="align-center"><br><figure class="post__image align-center"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/8/Screen-Shot-2020-11-02-at-14.36.31.png" sizes="(max-width: 48em) 100vw, 768px" srcset="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/8/responsive/Screen-Shot-2020-11-02-at-14.36.31-xs.png 300w ,https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/8/responsive/Screen-Shot-2020-11-02-at-14.36.31-sm.png 480w ,https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/8/responsive/Screen-Shot-2020-11-02-at-14.36.31-md.png 768w"  alt="" width="323" height="310"></figure><br><br>A project aiming at promoting Filipino Martial Arts, documenting my journey / training sessions.<br><br><br><figure class="post__image align-center"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/8/Screen-Shot-2020-11-02-at-14.35.46.png" sizes="(max-width: 48em) 100vw, 768px" srcset="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/8/responsive/Screen-Shot-2020-11-02-at-14.35.46-xs.png 300w ,https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/8/responsive/Screen-Shot-2020-11-02-at-14.35.46-sm.png 480w ,https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/8/responsive/Screen-Shot-2020-11-02-at-14.35.46-md.png 768w"  alt="" width="810" height="814"></figure><br><br><br><br><br><br></li>
</ul>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>About Us</title>
        <author>
            <name>SweetSeclusion</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://Hiraya.org/about-us/"/>
        <id>https://Hiraya.org/about-us/</id>

        <updated>2020-11-02T14:41:45+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p><!-- wp:coblocks/row {"columns":2,"layout":"66-33","coblocks":{"id":"55141317562"}} --></p>
<div class="wp-block-coblocks-row coblocks-row-55141317562" data-columns="2" data-layout="66-33">
<div class="wp-block-coblocks-row__inner has-medium-gutter has-no-padding has-no-margin is-stacked-on-mobile"><!-- wp:coblocks/column {"width":"60.00","coblocks":{"id":"55141320246"}} --><!-- wp:image {"id":403,"align":"center","width":343,"height":405} --><strong style="font-size: 14px; color: var(--text-editor-body-color); font-family: var(--font-base);"> <figure class="post__image align-left"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/3/Screen-Shot-2020-11-02-at-12.35.17-3.png" sizes="(max-width: 48em) 100vw, 768px" srcset="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/3/responsive/Screen-Shot-2020-11-02-at-12.35.17-3-xs.png 300w ,https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/3/responsive/Screen-Shot-2020-11-02-at-12.35.17-3-sm.png 480w ,https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/3/responsive/Screen-Shot-2020-11-02-at-12.35.17-3-md.png 768w"  alt="" width="1631" height="700"></figure><br><br>HIRAYA INTERNATIONAL </strong><span style="font-size: 14px; color: var(--text-editor-body-color); font-family: var(--font-base); font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);">is a Non-Profit Organization, bridging Romania, France, and the Philippines through knowledge sharing, culture and arts participation, and sustainable development.<br><br></span><span style="font-size: 14px; color: var(--text-editor-body-color); font-family: var(--font-base); font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);">The objective of </span><strong style="font-size: 14px; color: var(--text-editor-body-color); font-family: var(--font-base);">Hiraya International </strong><span style="font-size: 14px; color: var(--text-editor-body-color); font-family: var(--font-base); font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);">is to cultivate friendship and collaboration between Filipinos, French, and Romanians through cultural, artistic, gastronomic, and sporting events that highlight the uniqueness of each culture. It also aims to promote involvement in activities that supports sustainable development.</span><br><br><br></div>
</div>
<div class="wp-block-coblocks-row coblocks-row-77123959945" data-columns="2" data-layout="66-33">
<div class="wp-block-coblocks-row__inner has-medium-gutter has-no-padding has-no-margin is-stacked-on-mobile">
<div class="wp-block-coblocks-column coblocks-column-771240519" style="text-align: left; width: 45.55%;">
<div class="wp-block-coblocks-column__inner has-no-padding has-no-margin">
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
</div>
</div>
<p><!-- /wp:coblocks/column --></p>
</div>
</div>
<p><!-- /wp:coblocks/row --></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Contact Us</title>
        <author>
            <name>SweetSeclusion</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://Hiraya.org/contact-us/"/>
        <id>https://Hiraya.org/contact-us/</id>

        <updated>2020-09-29T17:12:12+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     Get in touch and we'll get back to you as soon as we can. We look forward to hearing&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Get in touch and we'll get back to you as soon as we can.  We look forward to hearing from you!</p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:heading --></p>
<h2>Contact Form</h2>
<p><!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Fields marked with an&nbsp;*&nbsp;are required</p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:spacer {"height":20} --></p>
<div style="height:20px" aria-hidden="true" class="wp-block-spacer"></div>
<p><!-- /wp:spacer --></p>
<p><!-- wp:coblocks/row {"columns":2,"layout":"66-33","coblocks":{"id":"551462210"}} --></p>
<div class="wp-block-coblocks-row coblocks-row-551462210" data-columns="2" data-layout="66-33">
<div class="wp-block-coblocks-row__inner has-medium-gutter has-no-padding has-no-margin is-stacked-on-mobile"><!-- wp:coblocks/column {"width":"60.00","coblocks":{"id":"5514624728"}} --></p>
<div class="wp-block-coblocks-column coblocks-column-5514624728" style="width:60.00%">
<div class="wp-block-coblocks-column__inner has-no-padding has-no-margin"><!-- wp:coblocks/form --><br />
<!-- wp:coblocks/field-name /--></p>
<p><!-- wp:coblocks/field-email {"required":true} /--></p>
<p><!-- wp:coblocks/field-textarea {"required":true} /--><br />
<!-- /wp:coblocks/form --></div>
</div>
<p><!-- /wp:coblocks/column --></p>
<p><!-- wp:coblocks/column {"width":"39.00","coblocks":{"id":"5514624733"}} --></p>
<div class="wp-block-coblocks-column coblocks-column-5514624733" style="width:39.00%">
<div class="wp-block-coblocks-column__inner has-no-padding has-no-margin"><!-- wp:contact-widgets/contact-block --></p>
<div class="wp-block-contact-widgets-contact-block">
<ul class="fields">
<li class="has-label">
<h4 class="contact-title">Send us a message</h4>
</li>
<li class="has-label">
<div><strong>Email<br/></strong>
<div class="contact-email"><a href="mailto:hello@hiraya.org">hello@hiraya.org</a></div>
</div>
</li>
</ul>
</div>
<p><!-- /wp:contact-widgets/contact-block --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></div>
</div>
<p><!-- /wp:coblocks/column --></div>
</div>
<p><!-- /wp:coblocks/row --></p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Home</title>
        <author>
            <name>SweetSeclusion</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://Hiraya.org/home/"/>
        <id>https://Hiraya.org/home/</id>

        <updated>2020-10-27T13:54:48+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    <p><!-- wp:columns {"className":"is-main-message"} --></p>
<div class="wp-block-columns has-2-columns is-main-message"><!-- wp:column -->
<div class="wp-block-column"><!-- wp:heading {"level":3,"customFontSize":21} -->
<h3 class="has-custom-size" style="font-size: 21px;">Welcome to Hiraya International</h3>
<p><!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph {"customFontSize":14} --></p>
<p class="has-custom-size" style="font-size: 14px;"><em>"Hiraya"</em> is an ancient Tagalog word that means <em>"dreams and hopes"</em> and here at Hiraya International, we dream of bridging the cultures of France, Romania, and the Philippines through different programs that highlight the three countries uniqueness.</p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph {"customFontSize":14} --></p>
<p class="has-custom-size" style="font-size: 14px;">Some of the things we want to promote are the Filipino Martial Arts, Romanian Folk Dances, and French organic agriculture.</p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
</div>
<p><!-- /wp:column --></p>
<p><!-- wp:column --></p>
<div class="wp-block-column"><!-- wp:image {"id":356,"align":"center","width":432,"height":448} -->
<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter is-resized"><figure class="wp-image-356"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/5/collaboration-community-cooperation-461049-1024x829.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 48em) 100vw, 768px" srcset="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/5/responsive/collaboration-community-cooperation-461049-1024x829-xs.jpg 300w ,https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/5/responsive/collaboration-community-cooperation-461049-1024x829-sm.jpg 480w ,https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/5/responsive/collaboration-community-cooperation-461049-1024x829-md.jpg 768w"  alt="" width="687" height="557"></figure></figure>
</div>
<p><!-- /wp:image --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
</div>
<p><!-- /wp:column --></p>
</div>
<p><!-- /wp:columns --></p>
<p><!-- wp:coblocks/row {"columns":2,"layout":"66-33","coblocks":{"id":"77123959945"}} --></p>
<div class="wp-block-coblocks-row coblocks-row-77123959945" data-columns="2" data-layout="66-33">
<div class="wp-block-coblocks-row__inner has-medium-gutter has-no-padding has-no-margin is-stacked-on-mobile"><!-- wp:coblocks/column {"width":"64.63","coblocks":{"id":"771240515"}} -->
<div class="wp-block-coblocks-column coblocks-column-771240515" style="width: 64.63%;">
<div class="wp-block-coblocks-column__inner has-no-padding has-no-margin"><!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
</div>
</div>
<p><!-- /wp:coblocks/column --></p>
<p><!-- wp:coblocks/column {"width":"34.37","coblocks":{"id":"771240519"}} --></p>
<div class="wp-block-coblocks-column coblocks-column-771240519" style="width: 34.37%;">
<div class="wp-block-coblocks-column__inner has-no-padding has-no-margin"><!-- wp:search {"label":""} /-->
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
</div>
</div>
<p><!-- /wp:coblocks/column --></p>
</div>
</div>
<p><!-- /wp:coblocks/row --></p>
<p><!-- wp:separator --></p>
<hr class="wp-block-separator"><!-- /wp:separator -->
<p><!-- wp:heading --></p>
<div class="gallery-wrapper"><div class="gallery"  data-is-empty="false" data-columns="3">
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/5/gallery/3-2.jpeg" data-size="768x1024"><img loading="lazy" src="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/5/gallery/3-2-thumbnail.jpeg" alt="" width="720" height="960"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/5/gallery/2-2.jpeg" data-size="768x1024"><img loading="lazy" src="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/5/gallery/2-2-thumbnail.jpeg" alt="" width="720" height="960"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/5/gallery/4-2.jpeg" data-size="768x1024"><img loading="lazy" src="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/5/gallery/4-2-thumbnail.jpeg" alt="" width="720" height="960"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/5/gallery/1-2.jpeg" data-size="1024x768"><img loading="lazy" src="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/5/gallery/1-2-thumbnail.jpeg" alt="" width="720" height="540"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/5/gallery/5-2.jpeg" data-size="1024x768"><img loading="lazy" src="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/5/gallery/5-2-thumbnail.jpeg" alt="" width="720" height="540"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/5/gallery/6-2.jpeg" data-size="1024x548"><img loading="lazy" src="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/5/gallery/6-2-thumbnail.jpeg" alt="" width="720" height="385"></a></figure>
</div></div>
<p><!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph {"customFontSize":14} --></p>
<p style="font-size: 14px;"><strong>HIRAYA INTERNATIONAL</strong> is an association, bridging Romania, France, and the Philippines through<br>knowledge sharing, culture and arts participation, and sustainable development and also to cultivate friendship and collaboration between Filipinos, French, and Romanians through cultural, artistic, gastronomic, and sporting events and projects that highlight the uniqueness of each culture.<br><br>To promote involvement in activities that supports sustainable development. to exchange knowledge in history, culture, arts, science, sports, and tourism; to build connections with cultural, professional, scientific, artistic, humanitarian, and literary groups; to create partnerships with financial-economic fields or cultural sponsorship; to create cultural exchange and dialogue through conferences, meetings, and talks.<br><br>To bolster artistic exchange through art events, sporting events, concerts, and exhibitions; to implement various programs in the arts like music, (sport, traditional and modern) dance and martial arts fit for different age groups; to participate in competitions, festivals, or congresses organized to promote artistic and cultural programs. To promote Filipino Martial Arts in Europe, Philippines and around the world.<br><br>To create public awareness of socio-political, community and environmental issues; to Promote a responsible attitude towards the environment among the general public; to promote, in cooperation with other specialized agencies, sustainable designs in the community; to promote nonpolluting technologies, renewable energy sources and organic farming; to support scientific researches that creates positive social and environmental impact; to support sustainable products and sustainable agricultural practices.<br><br>To organize humanitarian aid in the event of natural disasters, wars, and famines; to implement projects such as the construction of spaces that serve orphanages, nursing homes, social centers, homeless shelters, and or rehabilitation centers; to support projects of accessibility, sport and cultural activities for handicapped and marginalized sector.<br>To promote the culinary arts of each country through exhibitions and fairs; and to facilitate gastronomic<br>experiences with each culture; To promote the traditional food products of each country.<br><br></p>
<p><!-- /wp:coblocks/gallery-carousel --></p>
<p><!-- wp:separator --></p>
<hr class="wp-block-separator"><!-- /wp:separator -->
<p><!-- wp:paragraph {"customFontSize":14} --></p>
<p class="has-custom-size" style="font-size: 14px;"><br><br><strong>L’Association HIRAYA INTERNATIONAL</strong> c’est une association qui se propose de réunir la Roumanie, la<br>France et Philippines par l’échange des connaissances, les participations dans l’Arts et la culture et le<br>développement durable ainsi que cultiver l’amitié et la collaboration entre les citoyens philippinais, français, et roumains, à travers des évènements et projets culturelles, artistiques, gastronomiques et sportifs, pour mettre en évidence chaque culture.<br><br>Promouvoir l’implication dans les activités qui soutienent le développement durable; encourager l’échange de connaissances en histoire, culture, arts, science, sports et tourisme; établir des liens avec les groupes culturelles, professionnels, scientifiques, artistiques, humanitaires et littéraires; créer des parteneriats à domaines financier- économique ou des sponsorisations sportives; faciliter et de créer l’échange et le dialogue cuturel dans le cadre des conférences, rencontres ou débats.</p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph {"customFontSize":14} --></p>
<p class="has-custom-size" style="font-size: 14px;">Soutenir les échanges à travers des évenements artistiques, sportifs, concerts et expositions; implémenter divers programmes dans le domaine artistique comme la musique, la danse (traditionnel, modern, sportif) et les arts martiaux par diverses tranches d’âge; participer à des compétitions, festivals, ou d’organiser des congrés pour promouvoir des programmes artistiques et culturelles.<br><br>Promouvoir les Art Martiaux Philippins en Europe, Philippines et au monde entier.<br>Créer une prise de conscience publique concernant les problèmes socio-politiques, communautaires et de<br>l’environnement et de promouvoir une attitude responsible vis-à-vis de la nature dans le cadre de la population et de promouvoir, en coopération avec d’autres Agences et Organismes spécialisés, un design durable dans les communautées; Soutenir les recherches scientifiques qui ont un impact positif social et environemental, de promouvoir les technologies non-polluantes, les énergies renouvables et l’agriculture organique, les produits et les pratiques agricoles soutenables.<br><br>Organiser des campagnes d’aide humanitaire dans l’éventualité des désastres naturels, guerres, ou famine et d’implémenter des projets comme la contruction des espaces comme des orphelinates, asiles, centres sociaux, des abris pour les sdf, et des centres de réabilitation. De soutenir des projets d’accesssibilité, activités sportives et culturelles pour personnes handicapées et le secteur de la population marginalisé.<br><br>Promouvoir les arts culinaires de chaque pays à travers des expositions et des foires; faciliter les expériences gastronomiques avec chaque culture; Promouvoir les produits alimentaires traditionnels de chaque pays.<br><br></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph {"customFontSize":14} --></p>
<p class="has-custom-size" style="font-size: 14px;">Asociaţia <strong>HIRAYA INTERNATIONAL</strong> îşi propune să unească România, Franţa şi Filipine prin intermediul<br>schimbului de cunoştiinţe, participarea în arte şi cultură, şi dezvoltarea durabilă si de asemenea de a cultiva<br>prietenia şi colaborarea între cetăţenii filipinezi, francezi şi cei români prin evenimente şi proiecte culturale,<br>artistice, gastronomice şi sportive, care să scoată în evidenţă unicitatea fiecărei culturi.<br>Să promoveze implicarea în activităţi care să sprijine dezvoltarea durabilă a relatiilor intre cele trei state; să<br>incurajeze schimbul de cunoştiinţe în istorie, cultură, arte, ştiinţă, sport, şi turism; să construiască legături cu grupuri culturale, profesionale, ştiinţifice, artistice, humanitare şi literare; să creeze parteneriate cu domenii financiar-economice sau sponsorizări sportive; să faciliteze si creeze schimbul şi dialogul cultural în cadrul unor conferinţe, întâlniri şi discuţii.<br><br>Să susţină schimburi artistice prin intermediul evenimentelor artistice, sportive, concerte şi expoziţii; să<br>implementeze diferite programe în domenii artistice cum ar fi muzica, dansul (tradiţional, sportiv sau modern) şi artele marţiale pentru diferite segmente de vârstă; să participe în competiţii, festivaluri, sau congrese organizate pentru a promova programe artistice şi culturale. Să promoveze artele marţiale filipineze în Europa, Filipine şi restul lumii.<br><br>Să creeze o conştientizare publică asupra nivel problemelor socio-politice, comunitare şi de mediu şi să promoveze o atitudine responsabilă faţă de mediul înconjurător în cadrul populaţiei şi să promoveze, în cooperare cu alte agenţii şi organisme specializate, un design durabil în cadrul comunităţii; Să sprijine cercetările ştiinţifice care au un impact pozitiv social şi de mediu, să promoveze tehnologiile non-poluante, sursele de energie renovabile şi agricultura organică; să sprijine produse şi practici agricole sustenabile.<br><br>Să organizeze campanii de ajutorare umanitara în eventualitatea unor dezastre naturale, războaie, sau foamete şi să implementeze proiecte cum ar fi construcţia de spaţii care să servească drept orfelinate, azile, centre sociale, adăposturi pentru cei fără adăpost, sau centre de reabilitare. Să sprijine proiecte de accesibilitate, activităţi sportive şi culturale pentru persoanele cu handicap şi sectorul de populaţie marginalizată.<br><br>Să promoveze artele culinare ale fiecărei ţări prin intermediul de târguri şi expoziţii; şi să faciliteze experienţe gastronomice cu fiecare cultură; Să promoveze produsele şi mâncarea tradiţionale caracteristice<br>fiecărei ţări;</p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:more --></p>

                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p><!-- wp:columns {"className":"is-main-message"} --></p>
<div class="wp-block-columns has-2-columns is-main-message"><!-- wp:column -->
<div class="wp-block-column"><!-- wp:heading {"level":3,"customFontSize":21} -->
<h3 class="has-custom-size" style="font-size: 21px;">Welcome to Hiraya International</h3>
<p><!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph {"customFontSize":14} --></p>
<p class="has-custom-size" style="font-size: 14px;"><em>"Hiraya"</em> is an ancient Tagalog word that means <em>"dreams and hopes"</em> and here at Hiraya International, we dream of bridging the cultures of France, Romania, and the Philippines through different programs that highlight the three countries uniqueness.</p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph {"customFontSize":14} --></p>
<p class="has-custom-size" style="font-size: 14px;">Some of the things we want to promote are the Filipino Martial Arts, Romanian Folk Dances, and French organic agriculture.</p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
</div>
<p><!-- /wp:column --></p>
<p><!-- wp:column --></p>
<div class="wp-block-column"><!-- wp:image {"id":356,"align":"center","width":432,"height":448} -->
<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="aligncenter is-resized"><figure class="wp-image-356"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/5/collaboration-community-cooperation-461049-1024x829.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 48em) 100vw, 768px" srcset="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/5/responsive/collaboration-community-cooperation-461049-1024x829-xs.jpg 300w ,https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/5/responsive/collaboration-community-cooperation-461049-1024x829-sm.jpg 480w ,https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/5/responsive/collaboration-community-cooperation-461049-1024x829-md.jpg 768w"  alt="" width="687" height="557"></figure></figure>
</div>
<p><!-- /wp:image --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
</div>
<p><!-- /wp:column --></p>
</div>
<p><!-- /wp:columns --></p>
<p><!-- wp:coblocks/row {"columns":2,"layout":"66-33","coblocks":{"id":"77123959945"}} --></p>
<div class="wp-block-coblocks-row coblocks-row-77123959945" data-columns="2" data-layout="66-33">
<div class="wp-block-coblocks-row__inner has-medium-gutter has-no-padding has-no-margin is-stacked-on-mobile"><!-- wp:coblocks/column {"width":"64.63","coblocks":{"id":"771240515"}} -->
<div class="wp-block-coblocks-column coblocks-column-771240515" style="width: 64.63%;">
<div class="wp-block-coblocks-column__inner has-no-padding has-no-margin"><!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
</div>
</div>
<p><!-- /wp:coblocks/column --></p>
<p><!-- wp:coblocks/column {"width":"34.37","coblocks":{"id":"771240519"}} --></p>
<div class="wp-block-coblocks-column coblocks-column-771240519" style="width: 34.37%;">
<div class="wp-block-coblocks-column__inner has-no-padding has-no-margin"><!-- wp:search {"label":""} /-->
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
</div>
</div>
<p><!-- /wp:coblocks/column --></p>
</div>
</div>
<p><!-- /wp:coblocks/row --></p>
<p><!-- wp:separator --></p>
<hr class="wp-block-separator"><!-- /wp:separator -->
<p><!-- wp:heading --></p>
<div class="gallery-wrapper"><div class="gallery"  data-is-empty="false" data-columns="3">
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/5/gallery/3-2.jpeg" data-size="768x1024"><img loading="lazy" src="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/5/gallery/3-2-thumbnail.jpeg" alt="" width="720" height="960"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/5/gallery/2-2.jpeg" data-size="768x1024"><img loading="lazy" src="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/5/gallery/2-2-thumbnail.jpeg" alt="" width="720" height="960"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/5/gallery/4-2.jpeg" data-size="768x1024"><img loading="lazy" src="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/5/gallery/4-2-thumbnail.jpeg" alt="" width="720" height="960"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/5/gallery/1-2.jpeg" data-size="1024x768"><img loading="lazy" src="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/5/gallery/1-2-thumbnail.jpeg" alt="" width="720" height="540"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/5/gallery/5-2.jpeg" data-size="1024x768"><img loading="lazy" src="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/5/gallery/5-2-thumbnail.jpeg" alt="" width="720" height="540"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/5/gallery/6-2.jpeg" data-size="1024x548"><img loading="lazy" src="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/5/gallery/6-2-thumbnail.jpeg" alt="" width="720" height="385"></a></figure>
</div></div>
<p><!-- /wp:heading --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph {"customFontSize":14} --></p>
<p style="font-size: 14px;"><strong>HIRAYA INTERNATIONAL</strong> is an association, bridging Romania, France, and the Philippines through<br>knowledge sharing, culture and arts participation, and sustainable development and also to cultivate friendship and collaboration between Filipinos, French, and Romanians through cultural, artistic, gastronomic, and sporting events and projects that highlight the uniqueness of each culture.<br><br>To promote involvement in activities that supports sustainable development. to exchange knowledge in history, culture, arts, science, sports, and tourism; to build connections with cultural, professional, scientific, artistic, humanitarian, and literary groups; to create partnerships with financial-economic fields or cultural sponsorship; to create cultural exchange and dialogue through conferences, meetings, and talks.<br><br>To bolster artistic exchange through art events, sporting events, concerts, and exhibitions; to implement various programs in the arts like music, (sport, traditional and modern) dance and martial arts fit for different age groups; to participate in competitions, festivals, or congresses organized to promote artistic and cultural programs. To promote Filipino Martial Arts in Europe, Philippines and around the world.<br><br>To create public awareness of socio-political, community and environmental issues; to Promote a responsible attitude towards the environment among the general public; to promote, in cooperation with other specialized agencies, sustainable designs in the community; to promote nonpolluting technologies, renewable energy sources and organic farming; to support scientific researches that creates positive social and environmental impact; to support sustainable products and sustainable agricultural practices.<br><br>To organize humanitarian aid in the event of natural disasters, wars, and famines; to implement projects such as the construction of spaces that serve orphanages, nursing homes, social centers, homeless shelters, and or rehabilitation centers; to support projects of accessibility, sport and cultural activities for handicapped and marginalized sector.<br>To promote the culinary arts of each country through exhibitions and fairs; and to facilitate gastronomic<br>experiences with each culture; To promote the traditional food products of each country.<br><br></p>
<p><!-- /wp:coblocks/gallery-carousel --></p>
<p><!-- wp:separator --></p>
<hr class="wp-block-separator"><!-- /wp:separator -->
<p><!-- wp:paragraph {"customFontSize":14} --></p>
<p class="has-custom-size" style="font-size: 14px;"><br><br><strong>L’Association HIRAYA INTERNATIONAL</strong> c’est une association qui se propose de réunir la Roumanie, la<br>France et Philippines par l’échange des connaissances, les participations dans l’Arts et la culture et le<br>développement durable ainsi que cultiver l’amitié et la collaboration entre les citoyens philippinais, français, et roumains, à travers des évènements et projets culturelles, artistiques, gastronomiques et sportifs, pour mettre en évidence chaque culture.<br><br>Promouvoir l’implication dans les activités qui soutienent le développement durable; encourager l’échange de connaissances en histoire, culture, arts, science, sports et tourisme; établir des liens avec les groupes culturelles, professionnels, scientifiques, artistiques, humanitaires et littéraires; créer des parteneriats à domaines financier- économique ou des sponsorisations sportives; faciliter et de créer l’échange et le dialogue cuturel dans le cadre des conférences, rencontres ou débats.</p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph {"customFontSize":14} --></p>
<p class="has-custom-size" style="font-size: 14px;">Soutenir les échanges à travers des évenements artistiques, sportifs, concerts et expositions; implémenter divers programmes dans le domaine artistique comme la musique, la danse (traditionnel, modern, sportif) et les arts martiaux par diverses tranches d’âge; participer à des compétitions, festivals, ou d’organiser des congrés pour promouvoir des programmes artistiques et culturelles.<br><br>Promouvoir les Art Martiaux Philippins en Europe, Philippines et au monde entier.<br>Créer une prise de conscience publique concernant les problèmes socio-politiques, communautaires et de<br>l’environnement et de promouvoir une attitude responsible vis-à-vis de la nature dans le cadre de la population et de promouvoir, en coopération avec d’autres Agences et Organismes spécialisés, un design durable dans les communautées; Soutenir les recherches scientifiques qui ont un impact positif social et environemental, de promouvoir les technologies non-polluantes, les énergies renouvables et l’agriculture organique, les produits et les pratiques agricoles soutenables.<br><br>Organiser des campagnes d’aide humanitaire dans l’éventualité des désastres naturels, guerres, ou famine et d’implémenter des projets comme la contruction des espaces comme des orphelinates, asiles, centres sociaux, des abris pour les sdf, et des centres de réabilitation. De soutenir des projets d’accesssibilité, activités sportives et culturelles pour personnes handicapées et le secteur de la population marginalisé.<br><br>Promouvoir les arts culinaires de chaque pays à travers des expositions et des foires; faciliter les expériences gastronomiques avec chaque culture; Promouvoir les produits alimentaires traditionnels de chaque pays.<br><br></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph {"customFontSize":14} --></p>
<p class="has-custom-size" style="font-size: 14px;">Asociaţia <strong>HIRAYA INTERNATIONAL</strong> îşi propune să unească România, Franţa şi Filipine prin intermediul<br>schimbului de cunoştiinţe, participarea în arte şi cultură, şi dezvoltarea durabilă si de asemenea de a cultiva<br>prietenia şi colaborarea între cetăţenii filipinezi, francezi şi cei români prin evenimente şi proiecte culturale,<br>artistice, gastronomice şi sportive, care să scoată în evidenţă unicitatea fiecărei culturi.<br>Să promoveze implicarea în activităţi care să sprijine dezvoltarea durabilă a relatiilor intre cele trei state; să<br>incurajeze schimbul de cunoştiinţe în istorie, cultură, arte, ştiinţă, sport, şi turism; să construiască legături cu grupuri culturale, profesionale, ştiinţifice, artistice, humanitare şi literare; să creeze parteneriate cu domenii financiar-economice sau sponsorizări sportive; să faciliteze si creeze schimbul şi dialogul cultural în cadrul unor conferinţe, întâlniri şi discuţii.<br><br>Să susţină schimburi artistice prin intermediul evenimentelor artistice, sportive, concerte şi expoziţii; să<br>implementeze diferite programe în domenii artistice cum ar fi muzica, dansul (tradiţional, sportiv sau modern) şi artele marţiale pentru diferite segmente de vârstă; să participe în competiţii, festivaluri, sau congrese organizate pentru a promova programe artistice şi culturale. Să promoveze artele marţiale filipineze în Europa, Filipine şi restul lumii.<br><br>Să creeze o conştientizare publică asupra nivel problemelor socio-politice, comunitare şi de mediu şi să promoveze o atitudine responsabilă faţă de mediul înconjurător în cadrul populaţiei şi să promoveze, în cooperare cu alte agenţii şi organisme specializate, un design durabil în cadrul comunităţii; Să sprijine cercetările ştiinţifice care au un impact pozitiv social şi de mediu, să promoveze tehnologiile non-poluante, sursele de energie renovabile şi agricultura organică; să sprijine produse şi practici agricole sustenabile.<br><br>Să organizeze campanii de ajutorare umanitara în eventualitatea unor dezastre naturale, războaie, sau foamete şi să implementeze proiecte cum ar fi construcţia de spaţii care să servească drept orfelinate, azile, centre sociale, adăposturi pentru cei fără adăpost, sau centre de reabilitare. Să sprijine proiecte de accesibilitate, activităţi sportive şi culturale pentru persoanele cu handicap şi sectorul de populaţie marginalizată.<br><br>Să promoveze artele culinare ale fiecărei ţări prin intermediul de târguri şi expoziţii; şi să faciliteze experienţe gastronomice cu fiecare cultură; Să promoveze produsele şi mâncarea tradiţionale caracteristice<br>fiecărei ţări;</p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:more --></p>
<!-- /wp:more -->
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Gallery</title>
        <author>
            <name>SweetSeclusion</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://Hiraya.org/gallery/"/>
        <id>https://Hiraya.org/gallery/</id>

        <updated>2020-09-29T17:12:12+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p><!-- wp:coblocks/gallery-masonry {"align":"wide","gridSize":"lrg"} --></p>
<div class="wp-block-coblocks-gallery-masonry alignwide">
<div class="coblocks-gallery has-caption-style-dark has-gutter">
<ul class="has-grid-lrg has-gutter-15 has-gutter-mobile-15">
<li class="coblocks-gallery--item">
<figure class="coblocks-gallery--figure"><figure class="wp-image-356"><img loading="lazy" src="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/6/collaboration-community-cooperation-461049-1024x829.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 48em) 100vw, 768px" srcset="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/6/responsive/collaboration-community-cooperation-461049-1024x829-xs.jpg 300w ,https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/6/responsive/collaboration-community-cooperation-461049-1024x829-sm.jpg 480w ,https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/6/responsive/collaboration-community-cooperation-461049-1024x829-md.jpg 768w"  alt="" data-id="356" data-link="https://hiraya.org/home/collaboration-community-cooperation-461049/" /></figure></figure>
</li>
<li class="coblocks-gallery--item">
<figure class="coblocks-gallery--figure"><figure class="wp-image-350"><img loading="lazy" src="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/6/asia-blue-blue-sky-902288-1024x683.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 48em) 100vw, 768px" srcset="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/6/responsive/asia-blue-blue-sky-902288-1024x683-xs.jpg 300w ,https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/6/responsive/asia-blue-blue-sky-902288-1024x683-sm.jpg 480w ,https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/6/responsive/asia-blue-blue-sky-902288-1024x683-md.jpg 768w"  alt="" data-id="350" data-link="https://hiraya.org/home/asia-blue-blue-sky-902288/" /></figure></figure>
</li>
<li class="coblocks-gallery--item">
<figure class="coblocks-gallery--figure"><figure class="wp-image-346"><img loading="lazy" src="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/6/adult-baby-care-226616-1024x800.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 48em) 100vw, 768px" srcset="https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/6/responsive/adult-baby-care-226616-1024x800-xs.jpg 300w ,https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/6/responsive/adult-baby-care-226616-1024x800-sm.jpg 480w ,https://Hiraya.org/media/posts/6/responsive/adult-baby-care-226616-1024x800-md.jpg 768w"  alt="" data-id="346" data-link="https://hiraya.org/home/adult-baby-care-226616/" /></figure></figure>
</li>
</ul>
</div>
</div>
<p><!-- /wp:coblocks/gallery-masonry --></p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Frequently Asked Questions (FAQ)</title>
        <author>
            <name>SweetSeclusion</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://Hiraya.org/frequently-asked-questions-faq/"/>
        <id>https://Hiraya.org/frequently-asked-questions-faq/</id>

        <updated>2020-09-29T17:12:12+08:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    This is where you should answer the most common questions prospective customers might have. It's a good idea to cover&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p><!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>This is where you should answer the most common questions prospective customers might have. It's a good idea to cover things like your return policy, product warranty info, shipping and returns, etc. Check out the examples below.</p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --><!-- wp:coblocks/dynamic-separator {"className":"is-style-fullwidth"} --><br />
<hr class="is-style-fullwidth wp-block-coblocks-dynamic-separator" style="height:50px"><!-- /wp:coblocks/dynamic-separator --><!-- wp:heading {"level":3} --><br />
<h3>What's your return policy?</h3>
<p><!-- /wp:heading --><!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Return any of our products--no questions asked--within 30 days of purchase. We even pay return shipping.</p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --><!-- wp:coblocks/dynamic-separator {"className":"is-style-fullwidth"} --><br />
<hr class="is-style-fullwidth wp-block-coblocks-dynamic-separator" style="height:50px"><!-- /wp:coblocks/dynamic-separator --><!-- wp:heading {"level":3} --><br />
<h3>Do you ship oversees and to P.O. boxes?</h3>
<p><!-- /wp:heading --><!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Yes, we'll ship your package anywhere that can accept deliveries.</p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --><!-- wp:coblocks/dynamic-separator {"className":"is-style-fullwidth"} --><br />
<hr class="is-style-fullwidth wp-block-coblocks-dynamic-separator" style="height:50px"><!-- /wp:coblocks/dynamic-separator --><!-- wp:heading {"level":3} --><br />
<h3>Do you have customer service?</h3>
<p><!-- /wp:heading --><!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Of course! Our friendly and knowledgeable customer services reps are available to answer your questions 24/7/365.</p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
